#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyen-trung-hieu-96b117135 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

CAN bus

Jira

Agile Methodologies

### Certifications

Professional Scrum Master I
Professional Scrum Product Owner I

# Nguyen Trung Hieu

Senior Software Test Engineer at Bosch

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

# Summary

Experienced Software Test Engineer in Embedded Engineering with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Prime, Steering, Microsoft PowerPoint, and Python (Programming Language). Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in electrical engineering and information technology from Vietnamese-German University.

# Experience

Bosch

Senior Software Test Engineer December 2019 - Present (5 years 5 months)

Vietnam

Interested with cars and software. Testing software in loop (SIL) for Electric Power Steering of vehicle.

apply CI/CD into testing

vECU integrator

Vietnamese-German University

4 years 4 months

Student

September 2015 - December 2019 (4 years 4 months)

Vietnam

[C++] project Banking system February 2017 - May 2017 (4 months)

Binh Duong new city

Allow users create accounts, log in and enter the balance. Also allow users change the infos, encode and decode password, print out in other text file.

VGU-Ultimate Frisbee Club Club President May 2017 - May 2018 (1 year 1 month)

#### Binh Duong new city

- Tournament logistic VGU One Day Hat 2017
- Administrator of VGU Ultimate Frisbee Club

https://www.facebook.com/VguUltimateFrisbeeClub

- - Tournament program team - VGU One Day Hat 2018

#### Nestlé

CSV program 2017

June 2017 - August 2017 (3 months)

University of Technology and Education

Soft skills practice and study

Knowledge achievement from CSV program:

topic 1 Search inside yourself - Explore career orientaion

topic 2 English Communication course phase 1 - instructor: Danny Colomer \_

KTDC Group

topic 3 Excellent techniques of building and management team

topic 4 Career action plan

topic 5 Go See Think Do

topic 6 Presentation basic skill (Knowledge)

topic 7 English Communication course phase 2 - instructor: Danny Colomer \_

KTDC Group

topic 8 Presentation basic skill (Practice)

# UTE - University of Technology and Education Summer Intern

July 2016 - September 2016 (3 months)

Thủ Đức district, HCMC

- Soldering: creating a cube and a car model by soldering copper wire.
- Electricity equipment: studying and creating some industrial circuits by using timer, contactor, thermal relay, MCB, 3 phase AC motors,
- Electronics printed circuit board (PCB): creating a PCB of Miniature Circuit Breaker, using autodesk Eagle software

Vietnamese ger Anti Thief Locker project March 2016 - May 2016 (3 months)

Binh Duong new city

Using edison microcontroller, this project allow use type the password using module keyboard 4x4.

It include camera taking photo of intruders and send the photo to user email. Language using: Python, HTML

# Education

Vietnamese-German University
Bachelor's degree, electrical engineering and information technology · (2015 - 2019)